<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Aditi&#x27;s Space</title>
    <link href="https://aditichoudhary27.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://aditichoudhary27.github.io" />
    <updated>2020-04-15T00:33:42+05:30</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Aditi Choudhary</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://aditichoudhary27.github.io</id>

    <entry>
        <title>What Have We Here</title>
        <author>
            <name>Aditi Choudhary</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://aditichoudhary27.github.io/fancy-seeing-you-here.html"/>
        <id>https://aditichoudhary27.github.io/fancy-seeing-you-here.html</id>

        <updated>2020-04-15T00:33:37+05:30</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://aditichoudhary27.github.io/media/posts/2/IMG_20191027_123417.jpg" alt="" />
                    Greetings! The featured picture up there is one of my favourite shots, and&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://aditichoudhary27.github.io/media/posts/2/IMG_20191027_123417.jpg" alt="" />
                <p>Greetings! </p>
<p>The featured picture up there is one of my favourite shots, and in my opinion a very good way to start this off. This is me right here:</p>
<p><img class="post__image" src="https://aditichoudhary27.github.io/media/posts/2/IMG_20200308_180153__01.jpg" alt="" width="406" height="501"></p>
<p>I am also very excited about writing my first blog post. It's a little scary because I've never put more than a couple of sentences out there for people to read, given my previous understanding that I won't be writing very well to begin with. </p>
<p>So I see my doubts, and I raise them two arguments: One, it was one of my goals this year to step out of my comfort zone (which is a slightly enhanced word for hints of social anxiety) and I don't intend for doubts to hold me back. Two, it's my website. Even if I start this off with average writing and average photography, I have enough confidence for about four people combined that I'll get better. </p>
<p>I have a tons of plans for this website. The newsletter for sure, lots of photography, series of projects I decide to take on, thoughts about marketing, perhaps even consulting at some point and I'm sure I can think of other things later. </p>
<p>This exact point right here is my entire progress in three days -for one post- as I continue to sit and think if my writing is too informal to actually go out there. I'm very curious to see how it changes as I understand my own spectrum of thought. So if nothing else, this site is going to be my personal archive for progress in a lot of things. </p>
<p>I'm excited. This is going to be fun, guys. </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Pictures from my balcony </title>
        <author>
            <name>Aditi Choudhary</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://aditichoudhary27.github.io/photography.html"/>
        <id>https://aditichoudhary27.github.io/photography.html</id>

        <updated>2020-04-09T19:17:27+05:30</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://aditichoudhary27.github.io/media/posts/1/DSC02195.JPG" alt="" />
                <img class="post__image" src="https://aditichoudhary27.github.io/media/posts/1/DSC02193.JPG" alt="" width="5184" height="2920">
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
